Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics records, 1875-1979
Cornell University, New York State College of Home Economics records,
- Series XII. Printed Material
  - Cornell Extension Bulletins
    - Farm Women Look at the Home Bureau, 1948-09 (Box 67)
    - Color in the Home, 1948 (Box 67)
    - Hand-Finishing Your Dress, 1948-10 (Box 67)
    - Make Your Own Chair Covers(oversized bulletin, 1948-10 (Box 67)
    - The Arrangement of Home Furnishings, 1948-11 (Box 98)
    - Let's Prepare a Publication, 1949-01 (Box 67)
    - List of Publications, 1949-04 (Box 67)
    - The Japanese Beetle, 1949-07 (Box 98)
    - Pressing in Dressmaking, 1949-08 (Box 67)
    - Kitchen Cupboards that Simplify Storage, 1949-09 (Box 104)
    - Kitchen Cupboards that Simplify Storage, 1949-09 (Box 98)
    - Basting Your Dress, 1949-09 (Box 67)
    - Family Meal Service, 1949-11 (Box 104)
    - Soaps and other Detergents, 1949-11 (Box 67)
    - The Woman and Her Posture, 1950-02 (Box 98)
    - The Home-Freezing of Farm Products, 1950-04 (Box 67)
    - Simple Repairs of Upholstered Furniture, 1950-05 (Box 104)
    - Wills and Other Ways to Transfer Property to Heirs, 1950-05 (Box 67)
    - Simple Repairs of Upholstered Furniture, 1950-05 (Box 67)
    - Cane Seats for Chairs, 1950-05 (Box 109)
    - Home Canning of Fruits and Vegetables, 1950-06 (Box 67)
    - Meals for Paying Guests, 1950-07 (Box 67)
    - Household Cleaning, 1950-08 (Box 67)
    - Tomatoes the Year 'Round, 1950-08 (Box 104)
    - The Adolescent: Physical Development, 1950-09 (Box 98)
    - Spot and Stain Removal, 1950-09 (Box 98)
    - Purchasing Food for Fifty, 1950-11 (Box 109)
    - A Simple Way to Iron a Shirt, 1950-11 (Box 98)
    - Three Centuries of Furniture, 1950-11 (Box 67)
    - Outdoor Fireplaces, 1950-11 (Box 67)
    - Landscape Steep Slopes, 1950-11 (Box 67)
    - Good Cooking with Dry Milk, 1951-02 (Box 67)
    - Home-Grown Lumber for Farm Buildings, 1951-02 (Box 98)
    - Party Service, 1951-03 (Box 104)
    - Let Your Kitchen Arrangement Work for You, 1951-04 (Box 67)
    - Modern Hooked Rugs (oversized bulletin), 1951-04 (Box 67)
    - Family Meal Service, 1951-04 (Box 104)
    - Jellies and Jams, 1951-05 (Box 67)
    - Center for Your Work and Leisure, 1951-05 (Box 67, 104)
    - Marmalades, Preserves, Conserves, and Butters, 1951-06 (Box 104)
    - Molasses, 1951-07 (Box 67)
    - Home Care of the Sick, 1951-07 (Box 67)
    - Kitchen Cupboards That Simplify Storage, 1951-07 (Box 67)
    - Foods from the Freezer: Precooked and Prepared, 1951-08 (Box 104)
    - Bedding, 1951-09 (Box 67)
    - Helping Michael to Help Himself, 1951-09 (Box 67)
    - Homemade Sauerkraut, 1951-09 (Box 67)
    - How to Make Draperies, 1951-09 (Box 67)
    - Carpentry Tools, 1951-10 (Box 67)
    - Culinary Herbs, 1951-10 (Box 67)
    - Driveways and Sidewalks, 1951-11 (Box 67)
    - You Take It From Here, 1951-11 (Box 98)
    - Gardening For Better Living, 1952-02 (Box 104)
    - Growing Older, 1952-02 (Box 67)
    - Refinishing Old Furniture, 1952-02 (Box 67)
    - Soldering, 1952-03 (Box 67)
    - Repair of Innerspring Cushions, 1952-03 (Box 67)
    - The Japanese Beetle, 1952-04 (Box 104)
    - Safe Home Wiring and Electric Cords, 1952-05 (Box 104)
    - Good Cooking with Dry Milk, 1952-05 (Box 67)
    - These Are Working Mothers, 1952-06 (Box 98)
    - How to Make Cupboard Storage Devices, 1952-06 (Box 67)
    - Tomatoes the Year Round, 1952-08 (Box 67)
    - The Planting and Care of Shrubs and Trees, 1952-10 (Box 98)
    - A Simple Way to Iron a Shirt, 1952-11 (Box 104)
    - Homemade Playthings, 1953-02 (Box 98)
    - Care and Adjustment of the Sewing Machine, 1953-02 (Box 67)
    - Pressing Equipment, 1953-03 (Box 98)
    - Suggestions for Cornell Child and Adult Study Clubs, 1953-04 (Box 67)
    - Candied Fruits and Fruit Candy, 1953-05 (Box 67)
    - Braided Rugs, 1953-05 (Box 104)
    - Dresser Drawer Storage, 1953-05 (Box 67)
    - Clothing for Children, 1953-05 (Box 98)
    - Repair of Innerspring Cushions, 1953-05 (Box 104)
    - When you Work with Rayon and Acetate, 1953-06 (Box 67)
    - How to Make Fabric Buttonholes, 1953-06 (Box 67)
    - Barbecued Chicken, 1953-07 (Box 104)
    - Cake Decorating, 1953-09 (Box 104)
    - Easy to Make Bread and Rolls, 1953-10 (Box 104)
    - Christmas Decorations, 1953-10 (Box 67)
    - Food Makes a Difference, 1953-10 (Box 67)
    - When you Work with Rayon and Acetate, 1953-10 (Box 67)
    - Let Your Kitchen Arrangement Work for You, 1953-11 (Box 104)
    - How to Repair Wood Finishes, 1953-11 (Box 67)
    - Mending Clothes and Household Fabrics, 1954-01 (Box 104)
    - How to Make Fabric Buttonholes, 1954-01 (Box 67)
    - Driveways and Sidewalks, 1954-04 (Box 67)
    - A Kitchen-Dining Area Storage Wall, 1954-04 (Box 67)
    - How to Prepare and Cook Chicken, 1954-05 (Box 67)
    - Delicious Dishes From Dairy Products, 1954-05 (Box 67)
    - Salads-Cool, Crisp and Colorful, 1954-06 (Box 67)
    - The Care of Plants in the Home, 1954-06 (Box 104)
    - The Culture of Garden Chrysanthemums, 1954-06 (Box 104)
    - Let's Tell Our Story, 1954-07 (Box 67)
    - Safe Home Wiring and Electric Cords, 1954-07 (Box 67)
    - Let's Eat Eggs, 1954-07 (Box 67)
    - Home Laundering, 1954-08 (Box 98)
    - Community Meals, 1954-08 (Box 67)
    - The Adolescent:Physical Development, 1954-09 (Box 107)
    - List of Publications, 1954 (Box 67)
    - Party Service, 1955-01 (Box 67)
    - Control of the Dutch Elm Disease, 1955-02 (Box 104)
    - Potato Production, 1955-03 (Box 67)
    - Dresser Drawer Storage, 1955-05 (Box 67)
    - Fish Facts and Recipes, 1955-05 (Box 67)
    - Helping Michael to Help Himself, 1955-05 (Box 107)
    - Easy to Make Bread and Rolls, 1955-05 (Box 107)
    - Make Your Furs Wear Longer, 1955-06 (Box 104)
    - Cane Seats for Chairs, 1955-07 (Box 109)
    - Splint Seats for Chairs, 1955-07 (Box 109)
    - Border Plantings and Outdoor Living Rooms for Rural and Urban Properties, 1955-07 (Box 98)
    - Quick and Easy Rolls and Sweet Yeast Breads, 1955-07 (Box 67)
    - Sheets and Pillowcases:Selection, Use and Care, 1955-07 (Box 67)
    - Jellies and Jams, 1955-08 (Box 67)
    - What Height for Your Separate Electric Oven?, 1955-09 (Box 67)
    - You can do Block Painting, 1955-09 (Box 67)
    - Ways to Transfer Property to Heirs, 1955-09 (Box 104)
    - Quick Breads, 1955-10 (Box 67)
    - Homemaker, VIP, 1955-10 (Box 67)
    - Fun for Your Family, 1955-11 (Box 67)
    - Principles for Child Guidance, 1955-11 (Box 107)
    - List of Publications, 1955 (Box 104)
    - Care of Rugs and Carpets, 1956-01 (Box 67)
    - Know Your Concrete, 1956-02 (Box 67)
    - A Housecleaning Handbook, 1956-03 (Box 104)
    - Your New York State Extension Service, 1956-03 (Box 104)
    - Kitchen Cupboards that Simplify Storage, 1956-03 (Box 98)
    - How to Reline a Coat, 1956-05 (Box 67)
    - How to Make Cupboard Storage Devices, 1956-05 (Box 107)
    - Community Meals, 1956-06 (Box 107)
    - Home Canning of Fruits and Vegetables, 1956-08 (Box 104)
    - How to Clean Wallpaper, Walls and Woodwork, 1956-08 (Box 67)
    - Hong Kong Grass, Rope and Twine-seats for chairs, 1956-08 (Box 67)
    - How to Clean and Care for Plastics, 1956-08 (Box 104)
    - How to Care for the Glass and Metals in Your Home, 1956-08 (Box 107)
    - When You're a Leader, 1956-09 (Box 67)
    - Your New York State Extension Service, 1956-09 (Box 67)
    - Pillows:Selection, Use and Care, 1956-10 (Box 107)
    - Let's Eat Poultry, 1956-12 (Box 67)
    - Sleeves, 1956-12 (Box 67)
    - How to Join the Blouse and Skirt, 1956-12 (Box 67)
    - Cakes, Cookies and Pies, 1957-01 (Box 67)
    - Let Your Kitchen Arrangement Work for You, 1957-02 (Box 67)
    - How to Reline a Coat, 1957-02 (Box 67)
    - The Rock Garden, 1957-02 (Box 98)
    - A Simple Way to Iron a Shirt, 1957-04 (Box 98)
    - How to Dust and Clean Furniture, 1957-04 (Box 67)
    - How to Clean and Care for Plastics, 1957-04 (Box 67)
    - Cleaning Supplies, 1957-04 (Box 67)
    - Rush Seats for Chairs, 1957-05 (Box 109)
    - Cake Decorating, 1957-05 (Box 67)
    - Cooking Frozen Meats, Poultry, Game and Fish, 1957-07 (Box 67)
    - Today's Fabrics, 1957-07 (Box 67)
    - Brighten the Family Wash, 1957-07 (Box 107)
    - Know Your Community, August 1957 (Box 98)
    - Webbing Seats for Chairs, 1957-09 (Box 67)
    - Home Methods of Stain Removal, 1957-10 (Box 67)
    - How to Make Braided Rugs, 1957-11 (Box 98)
    - The Culture of the Delphinium, 1957-12 (Box 104)
    - New York State's Contribution to the Organization and Development of the County Agent Farm Home Bureau, 1957-12 (Box 67)
    - Marmalades, Preserves, Conserves and Butters, 1958-01 (Box 67)
    - Home Lawns, 1958-03 (Box 98)
    - The Culture of Gladiolus, 1958-04 (Box 104)
    - Collars and Cuffs, 1958-04 (Box 67)
    - Egg Rooms-Grading, Packing, Holding, 1958-06 (Box 67)
    - Outdoor Fireplaces, 1958-06 (Box 104)
    - Ways to Transfer Property to Heirs, 1958-08 (Box 67)
    - Posture and Foundation Garments, 1958-08 (Box 67)
    - Favorite Apple Recipes, 1958-08 (Box 67)
    - Christmas Tree Farming, 1958-09 (Box 67)
    - Wartime and Other Emergency Activities of the New York State Extension Service, 1958-09 (Box 98)
    - Freezing Fruit, 1958-09 (Box 109)
    - How to Control Your Weight, 1958-10 (Box 98)
    - Milk for your Family, 1958-11 (Box 67)
    - The Culture of Spring Flowering Bulbs, 1958-11 (Box 98)
    - How to Repair Wood Finishes, 1958-12 (Box 67)
    - Growing Older, 1958-12 (Box 107)
    - Passover Meals, 1959 (Box 109)
    - A list of Ornamental Plants for New York Seashores, 1959-02 (Box 104)
    - Party Service, 1959-02 (Box 67)
    - The Culture and Use of Ornamental Gourds, 1959-02 (Box 98)
    - Killing Undesirable Woody Plants With Chemicals, 1959-03 (Box 104)
    - Selecting Equipment for your Community Kitchen, 1959-03 (Box 67)
    - A Book List for Parents, 1959-04 (Box 67)
    - Cooking Frozen Vegetables and Fruits, 1959-04 (Box 67)
    - A Housecleaning Handbook, 1959-05 (Box 107)
    - Club Members Together, 1959-07 (Box 109)
    - Meal Management With a Freezer, 1959-08 (Box 107)
    - How to Make a Terrarium, 1959-09 (Box 98)
    - How to Glue Furniture, 1959-09 (Box 104)
    - Arrangement of Kitchen Centers, 1959-09 (Box 107)
    - Home Laundering, 1959-11 (Box 67)
    - Foods from the Freezer: Precooked and Prepared, 1959-11 (Box 109)
    - List of Publications, 1960 (Box 104)
    - Diseases of Bearded Irises, 1960-1969 (Box 104)
    - How to Make Cupboard Storage Devices, 1960-04 (Box 104)
    - Cheese Buy it, Eat it, Enjoy it, 1960-04 (Box 67)
    - Pillows, Selection, Use and Care, 1960-04 (Box 67)
    - The Culture of Spring Flowering Bulbs, 1960-05 (Box 104)
    - Suburban Gardening, 1960-06 (Box 98)
    - How to Reline a Coat, 1960-06 (Box 104)
    - How Do Children Feel Toward Younger Brothers and Sisters?, 1960-06 (Box 67)
    - Hot Breads for your Community Meals, 1960-06 (Box 67)
    - Pies: Pastry Fillings Meringue, 1960-06 (Box 67)
    - Recreation for Meetings, 1960-06 (Box 67)
    - Corsages form Garden Flowers, 1960-06 (Box 67)
    - Freezing Meat, Poultry and Fish, 1960-06 (Box 107)
    - Milk: How to Buy, Store and Use it, 1960-08 (Box 67)
    - Using Maple Syrup, 1960-08 (Box 67)
    - Meal Planning the Easy Way, 1960-11 (Box 67)
    - Peony Culture, 1960-12 (Box 104)
    - Quick Breads and Cookies, 1960-12 (Box 109)
    - Home Lawns, 1961-03 (Box 104)
    - Potatoes-a Bargain in Nutrition, 1961-03 (Box 67)
    - Arrangement of Kitchen Centers, 1961-04 (Box 67)
    - How to Cook Vegetables, 1961-04 (Box 67)
    - Family Meal Service, 1961-04 (Box 104)
    - Freezing Fruits and Vegetables, 1961-04 (Box 107)
    - Desserts for your Community Meals, 1961-05 (Box 67)
    - Recommended Annual Flowers for New York State, 1961-06 (Box 98)
    - Culture of Rhododendrons in New York State, 1961-06 (Box 104)
    - The Culture of Iris, 1961-07 (Box 104)
    - Home Laundering, 1961-07 (Box 67)
    - Care and Use of Plants in the Home, 1961-08 (Box 104)
    - Fruit Spreads and Preserves, 1961-08 (Box 109)
    - Pillows, Selection, Use and Care, 1961-08 (Box 67)
    - Cupboard Storage Devices, 1961-11 (Box 104)
    - How to Control Your Weight, 1961-12 (Box 98)
    - Artificial Lighting For Decorative Plants, 1961-12 (Box 104)
    - Cookies for your Community Meals, 1961-12 (Box 67)
    - Meal Management with a Freezer, 1961-12 (Box 67)
    - Sanitary Food Handling in Church Community Center and Camp, 1961-12 (Box 67)
    - Propagation of House Plants, 1962-01 (Box 104)
    - Work Safely in Your Community Kitchen, 1962-01 (Box 67)
    - Community Buildings Food Service Equipment, 1962-02 (Box 67)
    - Care and Use of Plants in the Home, 1962-02 (Box 98)
    - Introduction to Home Gardening, 1962-02 (Box 98)
    - Forcing Shrubs and Trees for Indoor Bloom, 1962-02 (Box 98)
    - Flowers from Seed, 1962-02 (Box 104)
    - Ground Clovers, 1962-02 (Box 104)
    - The Compost Pile, 1962-02 (Box 104)
    - A Housecleaning Handbook, 1962-03 (Box 67)
    - Sleeves, 1962-04 (Box 67)
    - How to Join the Blouse and Skirt, 1962-04 (Box 67)
    - Cupboard Storage Devices, 1962-04 (Box 104)
    - Collars and Cuffs, 1962-05 (Box 67)
    - Home Canning of Meat and Poultry, 1962-05 (Box 67)
    - Mending Clothes and Household Fabrics, 1962-05 (Box 67)
    - Food Makes a Difference, 1962-06 (Box 67)
    - Shaping Christmas Trees for Quality, 1962-06 (Box 67)
    - Artificial Lighting for Decorative Plants, 1962-07 (Box 98)
    - Home Canning of Fruits and Vegetables, 1962-07 (Box 67)
    - Brighten the Family Wash, 1962-08 (Box 67)
    - Solving Cultural Troubles of Rhododendrons and Other Ericaceous Plants, 1962-08 (Box 104)
    - Dresser Drawer Storage, 1962-09 (Box 67)
    - Shoppers Handbook, 1962-09 (Box 67)
    - Fish and Shellfish, 1962-11 (Box 67)
    - Let's Cut Meat, 1963-01 (Box 109)
    - The Culture of Garden Roses, 1963-02 (Box 104)
    - Young Man Take A Clothes Look!, 1963-02 (Box 67)
    - Culinary Herbs, 1963-03 (Box 109)
    - Pressing Equipment, 1963-04 (Box 67)
    - Fruit Spreads and Preserves, 1963-06 (Box 67)
    - A Smooth Look in Sleeves, 1963-08 (Box 67)
    - Barbequed Chicken, 1963-09 (Box 104)
    - Shrubs for Landscape Plantings in New York State, 1963-10 (Box 104)
    - Research Methods for Study of Human Costs of Household Work: Development and Use at Cornell, 1963-12 (Box 67)
    - A Simple Way to Iron a Shirt, 1963-11 (Box 67)
    - Pillows ? Selection, Use and Care, 1963-12 (Box 67)
    - Freezing Cooked and Prepared Foods, 1964-01 (Box 67)
    - Shoppers' Handbook, 1964-01 (Box 67)
    - Nutritional Facts about Fats, 1964-01 (Box 104)
    - Freezing Meat, Poultry and Fish, 1964-02 (Box 67)
    - Principles for Child Guidance, 1964-05 (Box 104)
    - Water Safety, 1964-05 (Box 109)
    - How to Cook Vegetables, 1962-06 (Box 109)
    - How Clean Your Clothes, 1964-06 (Box 67)
    - Fabric Finishes for Beauty, Service, Protection, 1964-07 (Box 67)
    - Game Care and Preparation in the Field and Home, 1964-10 (Box 67)
    - Family Meal Service, 1964-11 (Box 67)
    - Growing and Marketing Christmas Trees, 1964-11 (Box 67)
    - Food Additives Their Role Today, 1964-11 (Box 67)
    - Freezing Fruits and Vegetables, 1964-12 (Box 67)
    - Sheets and Pillowcases, 1964-12 (Box 67)
    - Food Value Chart, 1965-03 (Box 67)
    - Home Fire Protection, 1965-03 (Box 104)
    - Propagation of House Plants, 1965-04 (Box 104)
    - Salads, Cool, Crisp, and Colorful, 1965-05 (Box 104)
    - Cheese-Buy It, Eat It, Enjoy It, 1965-05 (Box 109)
    - Common Wild Flowers of New York State, 1965-06 (Box 104)
    - The Versatile Egg, 1965-06 (Box 67)
    - Paying Your Bills, 1965-06 (Box 67)
    - Preview Your Spending, 1965-06 (Box 67)
    - Storing Your Money, 1965-06 (Box 67)
    - Yeast Bread and Rolls, 1965-07 (Box 109)
    - Fish and Shellfish, 1965-08 (Box 67)
    - Manage Your Way to Quicker Meals, 1965-08 (Box 67)
    - Housecleaning Handbook for Young Homemakers, 1965-10 (Box 104)
    - Nutrition Sense and Nonsense, 1966-01 (Box 104)
    - Facts About Floor Care, 1966-02 (Box 67)
    - Apples A Favorite Food, 1966-03 (Box 67)
    - Feeding the Family, 1966-05 (Box 67)
    - Do you Know Your Valuable Papers?, 1966-04 (Box 104)
    - Introduction to Home Gardening, 1966-04 (Box 67)
    - Your Work and Your Posture, 1966-05 (Box 67)
    - Principles for Child Guidance, 1966-05 (Box 98)
    - Raspberry Growing in New York State, 1966-06 (Box 104)
    - Facts About Underfashions, 1966-06 (Box 67)
    - Fabric Finishes for Beauty, Service and Protection, 1966-06 (Box 67)
    - A Food Value Wheel, 1966-08 (Box 104)
    - Yeast Bread and Rolls, 1966-10 (Box 104)
    - Food Additives Their Role Today, 1966-10 (Box 100)
    - How to Cook Vegetables, 1966-10 (Box 67)
    - Housecleaning Handbook for Young Homemakers, 1966-12 (Box 104)
    - Food Value Chart, 1966-12 (Box 67)
    - Nutrition Books: A Guide to Their Reliability, 1967-01 (Box 67)
    - Facts About Underfashions, 1967-01 (Box 67)
    - Introduction to Home Gardening, 1967-02 (Box 99)
    - In Shopping, In Cleaning: Be Smart about Cookware, 1967-03 (Box 67)
    - Fresh Fruits and Vegetables, 1967-03 (Box 67)
    - Play as Learning, 1967-05 (Box 67)
    - Handbook for Freezing Foods, 1967-06 (Box 109)
    - How to Glue Furniture, 1967-10 (Box 67)
    - Salads Cool, Crisp, and Colorful, 1967-10 (Box 67)
    - Striving for Independence, 1967-10 (Box 67)
    - Purchasing Food for 50 Servings, 1967-11 (Box 107)
    - Sanitary Food Handling in Church Community Center and Camp, 1967-12 (Box 107)
    - Cornell Extension Bulletins-Home Economics-List of titles, 1967 (Box 109)
    - Cornell Extension Bulletins-Agriculture-List of titles, 1967 (Box 109)
    - Times to Buy Meat, 1968-03 (Box 107)
    - Calorie Sense and Nonsense, 1968-04 (Box 104)
    - Cheese Buy it, Eat it, Enjoy it, 1968-06 (Box 67)
    - Container Culture of Ornamental Plants for the Home Grounds, 1968-07 (Box 99)
    - Principles for Child Guidance, 1968-11 (Box 67)
    - Films for Home Economists-List of titles, 1968 (Box 109)
    - Ground Covers for New York State Landscape Plantings (Box 98)
    - Shoppers' Handbook, 1969-01 (Box 67)
    - Trees for the Home Grounds, 1969-03 (Box 99)
    - Foundation Plantings About the House, 1969-03 (Box 99)
    - Manage Your Way to Quicker Meals, 1969-05 (Box 109)
    - What's in Home Cleaning Products?, 1969-06 (Box 67)
    - Shrubs for Landscape Plantings in New York State, 1969-07 (Box 104)
    - Functional Kitchens, 1969-07 (Box 67)
    - Four Nursery Schools, 1969-07 (Box 67)
    - Facts About Floor Care, 1969-09 (Box 67)
    - Cornell Extension Bulletins-Home Economics-List of titles, 1969 (Box 109)
    - Perspectives on Overweight, 1970-01 (Box 109)
    - Cornell Extension Bulletins-Home Economics-List of titles, 1970-02 (Box 109)
    - Nutrition Sense and Nonsense, 1970-02 (Box 98)
    - Safe Handling of Foods in Quantity, 1970-02 (Box 98)
    - Children's Shoes, 1970-06 (Box 104)
    - Children's Art, 1970-07 (Box 98)
    - Do You Know Your Valuable Papers?, 1970-08 (Box 67)
    - Foods for Health, 1970-08 (Box 67)
    - Alimentos Para Tu Salud, 1970-08 (Box 67)
    - The Care and Simple Repair of Household Equipment, 1970-09 (Box 67)
    - Housecleaning Handbook, 1971-01 (Box 67)
    - Cut Tulips for Commercial Growers from Dry-Stored, Pre-Cooled Bulbs, 1971-01 (Box 104)
    - Sequence of Bloom of Perennials, Biennials and Bulbs, 1971-02 (Box 104)
    - Home Lawns, 1971-03 (Box 99)
    - The Culture of Garden Chrysanthemums, 1971-06 (Box 104)
    - Children's Shoes, 1971-06 (Box 67)
    - The Culture and Use of Ornamental Gourds, 1971-09 (Box 104)
    - Yeast Bread and Rolls, 1972-01 (Box 67)
    - Ornamental Vines for Landscape Plantings in New York State, 1972-05 (Box 104)
    - Foods for Health-The Puerto Rican Food Wheel, 1972-07 (Box 109)
    - Artificial Lighting for Decorative Plants, 1972-09 (Box 104)
    - Landscape Design for Residential Property, 1973-02 (Box 104)
    - Home Lawns, 1973-02 (Box 67)
    - Rush Seats for Chairs, 1973-03 (Box 67)
    - Cane Seats for Chairs, 1973-05 (Box 67)
    - The Meeting Will Come to Order, 1973-06 (Box 67)
    - Barbequed Chicken, 1974-02 (Box 98)
    - Ground Covers for New York State Landscape Plantings, 1974-02 (Box 104)
    - Hongkong Grass, Rope and Twine, 1974-06 (Box 67)
    - Rush Seats for Chairs, 1974-09 (Box 104)
    - Perspectives on Overweight, 1975-03 (Box 67)
    - Handbook for Freezing Foods, 1975-03 (Box 67)
    - Methods and Tools for Effective Teaching, 1975-09 (Box 67)
    - How to Make a Terrarium, 1975-09 (Box 104)
    - The Meeting Will Come to Order, 1976-01 (Box 107)
    - Know How Catalog-List of titles of bulletins, booklets, packets and other printed material from the College of Human Ecology and the College of Agriculture, 1976-10 (Box 109)
    - Furniture Restoration (oversized bulletin, 1978-03 (Box 67)
    - Perspectives on Overweight, 1981-03 (Box 67)
    - Do You Know Your Valuable Papers?, 1981-07 (Box 67)
    - Hong Kong Grass, Rope and Twine, 1981-09 (Box 109)
    - Splint Seats for Chairs, 1988-01 (Box 109)
    - Rush Seats for Chairs, 1988-01 (Box 109)
    - Cane Seats for Chairs, 1994-12 (Box 109)
    - The Selection of Rugs and Carpets, undated (Box 67)
    - Favorite Apple Recipes, undated (Box 67)
  - Memoirs- Agricultural Experiment Station
    - Memoirs, 1943-03 (Box 67)
    - Use of Time by Full-time and Part-time Homemakers in Relation to Home Management, 1954-07 (Box 67)
    - Bleaching in the Home Laundry, 1954-06 (Box 67)
    - Homemaking Work Units for New York State Households, 1957-12 (Box 67)
    - Life History and Economic Relations of the Opossum in New York State, 1958-03 (Box 67)
    - Some Factors of Cost to the Body in Standing to Work and Sitting to Work Under Different Postural Conditions, 1959-06 (Box 67)
    - Supplementary Sinks in Home Kitchens, 1960-10 (Box 67)
    - Economic Contributions Made to Newly Married Couples by Their Parents, 1963-05 (Box 67)
    - Continuity of Household Work, 1963-06 (Box 67)
    - Properties, Qualities, and Characteristics of Most and Least Liked Household Tasks, 1963-07 (Box 67)
    - Personal Hygiene Attitudes and Practices in 1000 Middle-Class Households, 1965-08 (Box 67)
  - 4-H Club Members' and Club Leaders' Guides
    - Let's Have a Party-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1953 (Box 109)
    - 4-H Club Handyman-How to Apply a Painted Finish to Wood-Guide for Members, 1956-05 (Box 109)
    - Let's Help t Home-Leader's Guide, 1957 (Box 109)
    - Groom Your Room-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1957 (Box 109)
    - Clothing Handbook, 1957-07 (Box 46)
    - Care and Use of Paint Brushes, 1957-11 (Box 98)
    - Let's Help at Home, 1957 (Box 109)
    - Time for Lunch-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1957 (Box 109)
    - Tips for Waitresses-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1957 (Box 109)
    - Adventures in Dinners-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1957 (Box 109)
    - Fruit Delights-Leader's Guide, 1958 (Box 109)
    - Canning-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1958 (Box 109)
    - Freezing-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1958 (Box 109)
    - Care and Use of Paint Brushes, 1957-11 (Box 109)
    - Clothing Handbook, 1959-06 (Box 98)
    - Breakfast is Ready-Leader's and Member's Guides, 1960 (Box 109)
    - Guide to the Let's Sew Projects, 1962-03 (Box 98)
    - Let's Sew Blouses, 1962-06 (Box 98)
    - Let's Sew Skirts, 1962-06 (Box 98)
    - Let's Sew Costume Coordinates-Member's Guide, 1962-06 (Box 109)
    - This is 4-H-printed by USDA, 1962-10 (Box 109)
    - ABC's of Food-Leader's Guide, 1962 (Box 109)
    - Suds Your Duds, 1963-07 (Box 98)
    - Let's Sew Blouses-Member's Guide, 1963-08 (Box 98)
    - Guide to the Let's Sew Projects-Leader's Guide, 1963-08 (Box 109)